Today is Friday, extra fun.
The Stockholm Stock Exchange is up 1 %
Despite Brexitoro and possible confidence vote against May.
Intendo goes worse for, down 9 %.
Nibe is noticed among today's winners after a strong report.
I got a little heavy heapon because I'm so excited.
You are like a waiter with the tray.
We will talk about a bunch of companies with defensive growth.
It together with Fredrik Skoglund, welcome
And Viktor Hansson, welcome.
But first I want to ... Viktor Henriksson.
I'm just kidding.
I am so happy that we have his stove here
To make products, but high risk that it will be wrong.
Therefore, it is important that they have the right quality.
That is why we have invested in NCAB.
You look a little tired ... the order intake in the future ...
Q4 is a bad season and has always been a little worse
Regarding the Revenue.
But order intake is usually decent.
It depends on when the Chinese New Year falls
And the factories close in China.
Customers take it for it and order a little before.
We don't really know when the orders arrive.
We don't really know what's going on with the business cycle.
For us, the focus is new customers and markets
So it can be something positive about this.
Do you own NCAB, Viktor
Not at the moment.
But I have looked at the company on several occasions
And it is a very nice and well -managed company.
Impressive.
Do you have any question you just praise.
You are a little faster to a better margin in Europe
than thought previously.
Are there any structural differences to
Why the margin in Europe cannot reach the Nordic region?
In the Nordic countries we have been around for a very long time.
It feels like you are praising a giant efficiency.
Maybe you should start looking at cyclical companies.
What is on the stock exchange of defensive nature
There is not much to choose from.
I produced some such companies.
There is Tele2.
It is a heavenly well -managed company for an attractive valuation.
They are going to be out of the small corporation index
And some business must be approved.
I think there is an upside to the merger with Comhem.
Synergies.
Those synergies will probably increase pretty soon.
Maybe in connection with Q4 at the beginning of next year.
There is the potential to save more than they have gone out with.
We will probably see increased profit forecasts at the beginning of next year.
Then the share becomes even cheaper than now.
It is a well -managed company that is not affected by the business cycle.
Good direct return and places in a defensive portfolio.
Interesting.
You have an exciting list of companies.
Next is a relative, Millicom.
Like, stuck in South America.
Exactly.
Millicom is a cousin to Tele2
with the same principal and founder-
But I think they will succeed in the future.
On 5 times the operating profit should be able to be praised.
Have you looked at Millicom
A little.
I think it is very cheap.
Tele2 may be a couple of years ahead of Millicom
in his transformation.
Kinnevik probably makes a similar trip -
with Millicom.
It looks very cheap.
Speaking of cheap, Kinnevik and travel: MTG.
A lot to talk about.
I wrote it on the list for Fredrik to come.
And he was so happy.
It's also cheap.
Today you get MTGX for free.
Only Nordic Entertainment Group is worth the stock price.
And so MTGX will be knocked off in early 2019.
Esport is still exciting.
And innogames, a gaming company within MTGX
delivers amazing numbers.
The valuation is zero is well, to say the least.
The year has been dramatic for MTG.
First sales
of the television channels to Tele Denmark which was positive -
But was blown off and thus lowered the course.
Then Kinnevik distributed all mtg share -
to their shareholders.
And some of them-
Do not want the share, which gives price pressure.
And this summer, Telia bought TV4.
So business is done with television channels, even internationally.
So the availability of MTG's television channels
can be quite attractive.
And things can happen there.
Happens nothing, it won't be bought
Is it probably a stable business that provides good cash flow -
And as many want to own.
MTG may be new hoist.
Everyone talks up mtg
And then things don't go so well.
well -received both among international -
And Swedish investors.
The comparison is probably bad.
You are positive, both to Tele 2 and MTG.
Kinnevik, then, instead
Kinnevik has been hit
because Zalando has not praised the market lately.
But that's probably an opportunity.
We move on to security and cash handling.
You like Loomis.
Yes, a safe and stable company that is not affected
of business cycle and commodity prices.